<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
    <page_title>Ed's Web Photo Album Index</page_title>
    <entry>
        <title>August 2016 Rhine and Mosel River Cruise</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2016n-rhine-mosel-river-cruise/</url>
        <thumbnail>rhine-mosel.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            Starting with a stay in Bruges, Belgium, we cruised from Antwerp to Basel along the Rhine and Mosel rivers, stopping in lots of interesting cities along the way in Belgium, the Netherlands, Germany, and France and ending in Basel, Switzerland.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Summer 2015 Land/Cruise trip to Alaska</title>
        <url>https://goo.gl/photos/GFQnS7x8qxSNo3Kg8</url>
        <thumbnail>alaska.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             In spring of 2015, we decided on the spur of the moment to take an Alaska cruise in June and July. We had cruised in Hawaii with Norwegian and decided to go with their trip that starts on land in Fairbanks, down to Denali National Park and on to Anchorage, Homer and Seward before boarding the Norwegian Sun for a cruise through the inside passage to Vancouver, Canada. The land tour company was a great partner to Norwegian, and we made lots of friends on that part of the trip. 
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>October 2014 Trip to Alpine Europe</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2014j-alps-trip/</url>
        <thumbnail>alps.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             We spent three weeks in the Alps, starting in Italy staying on Lake Como, Milan, and Lake Maggiore, then moving on to Interlaken, Switzerland, taking a side trip to Zermatt on the way. After a few days there with some great day trips, we moved on to Seefeld, Austria via Vaduz, Liechtenstein. Finally, we moved on to a night in Munich, Germany for our flight home.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>December 2013 trip to Hawaii</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2013o-hawaii/</url>
        <thumbnail>hawaii.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             The week before Christmas in 2013, we took our first trip to Hawaii, visiting four islands and staying busy every day for a week. We slept and ate most meals on the the Norwegian Cruise Lines ship, Pride of America, and used their excursion booking service, which turned out very well. We are not really large cruise ship people, but this was about the best way we could find to get around the islands, and the staff did an excellent job with the logistics.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Aug, Sept 2013 trip to England, Wales, and Scotland</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2013k-uk-trip/</url>
        <thumbnail>london.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             We toured the UK for three weeks, starting in London, and ending in the Scottish Highlands. This album is not quite, so come back periodically to see our progress.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Andrea's Scrapbook of Stacey and Peter's Wedding</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2012i-stacey-wedding-scrapbook/</url>
        <thumbnail>stacey-wedding.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             Though they had quietly gotten married a few months before, this July 2012 ceremony was a full blown wedding attended by lots of friends and family members. Andrea made an electronic scrapbook from photos taken by multiple people, including their wedding photographer.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>September 2012 cruise on the River Seine with Grand Circle.</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2012l-france-cruise/</url>
        <thumbnail>paris.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             We toured Normandy with Beth and fellow Grand Circle travelers, starting in Paris and ending up in Honfleur, near the mouth of the river. This album is incomplete, but has pictures from the Paris part of the trip.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Summer 2011 trip to Yellowstone, Grand Tetons and Cody, WY</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2011c-yellowstone-trip/</url>
        <thumbnail>grand-tetons.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             We took a one-week road trip to Yellowstone National Park, Grand Teton National Park, Jackson Hole, and Cody, Wyoming in June 2011. We even got a chance to drive in snow to prepare for our move back to Massachusetts the following year.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Fall 2010 Ed, Andrea and Beth in Italy</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2010j-italy-trip/</url>
        <thumbnail>sorrentine-peninsula.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
             Andrea, Ed and Beth took a Grand Circle Travel tour of Rome, the Amalfi Coast, and Tuscany for three weeks in the the fall. Andrea says this is her favorite trip yet, and it was great to introduce Beth to this kind of travel.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>November 2009 Ed's trip to Egypt</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2009r-egypt-trip/</url>
        <thumbnail>giza.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            Ed took a Grand Circle Travel tour of Egypt for two weeks in the middle of November. This included a few days in Cairo with visits to important historical and cultural sites, followed by a cruise down the Nile from Aswan to Luxor. Besides visits to tombs and temples, highlights included sailing on the Nile and a hot air balloon ride near the Valley of the Kings.    
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>August 2009 A Week in Oregon with Bill and Roz</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2009m-billroz-visit/</url>
        <thumbnail>bill-and-roz.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            Our close friends from Massachusetts came to visit us for six days in Oregon. We spent the whole time playing tourist in Portland, the Gorge, Mount Saint Helens, the Oregon coast, and sailing on the Columbia River. We shared some of our favorite things to do, like sailboat racing, going to Kornblatt's deli, Powell's Books, Saturday Market, Seaside and Astoria, and also discovered Mount St. Helens together.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>July 2009 Olympia to Longbranch Cruise</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2009k-longbranch-cruise/</url>
        <thumbnail>longbranch-cruise.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            We took a two-day sailing cruise as part of a three boat flotilla from Olympia to Longbranch in the south Puget Sound in Washington. This was an activity of the Island Sailing Club's Cruising Group.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Summer 2008 Trip to Ukraine and Russia</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2008j-russia-trip/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>st-basils.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            We took a Grand Circle trip to Russia, including Moscow, a cruise on the Volga, and St. Petersburg. As a pre-trip, we went to Kiev, Ukraine. Rather than wait until I am finished with all of the pictures, I am building this site a day at a time, so check back often for more pictures.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Summer 2008 July 4 weekend in Massachusetts</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2008h-ma-trip/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>halibut-point.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            We went to Massachusetts for a little over a week, including the July 4 weekend, to visit our friends in the Boston area and Stacey in Northampton. The weather was sort of hot, humid and thundery, but we still had a good time. Four years later we moved back from Hillsboro, OR to Westborough, MA.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>April 2008 Road Trip to Arizona and Utah</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2008e-april-roadtrip/</url>
        <thumbnail>sedona.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            We took a 3500 mile road trip from our home near Portland, Oregon down through Oregon and Northern California to San Jose, across to the coast at Monterey Bay, down the coast to Morro Bay, across to Palm Springs and on to Tucson, where we visited Rachel for a few days. From there we went north to Sedona for a couple of days and on to St. George, Utah to visit Vickie and Don, Zion and Bryce. Finally, we made our way home with stops in Salt Lake City and Boise.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>March 2008 Antigua Sailing Vacation</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2008c-antigua/</url>
        <thumbnail>sunsail.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            We spent a week with about 100 fellow members of the American Sailing Association at Sunsail Club Colonna on Antigua in March. Bill and Roz joined us and we had a great time. This was our first "tropical paradise" vacation, and it is really not hard to get used to. We got a chance to sail a couple of big boats and try our hand at dinghy sailing, or in our case, dinghy capsizing. No matter, though, because the water was always warm and the dunking was refreshing.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jeff Watson Memorial road trip to Montana</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2006g-montana_trip/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>jeffw.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            Our nephew, Jeff, died suddenly in the fall of 2005 at 30 years of age, a great shock to the family. His parents, Vickie and Don, arranged a family memorial in Anaconda, Montana, a place where Jeff had spent some time and where he had planned on buying land.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Summer 2006 in Israel</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/Israel2006/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>akko.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            Ed spent six weeks at the Intel Israel Design Center in Haifa, and during the first couple of weekends played tourist. Later in the trip the political situation heated up and the 2006 Hezbollah war reached Haifa just as he was leaving.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>April 2006 in China</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/china2006/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>hutong.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            After having to cancel our trip to China in 2005, we finally made the trip, visiting Beijing, Shanghai, Xian, Guilin, Hong Kong, and a week on the Yangtze River. The first group posted is from in and around Beijing, including Tiananmen Square, The Forbidden City, The Temple of Heaven, The Summer Palace, a tour of a Hutong (traditional Beijing neighborhood), a trip to the Beijing Opera, a visit to a Cloisonne factory (Shopping!), the Great Wall of China and the Ming Dynasty emporer's tombs. Album still under construction.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>December 2005 in Arizona</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/arizona2005/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>cactus.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
           After moving to Oregon, this was our first trip out of state. We took a long weekend in Tucson to hear Rachel's chorus sing and see where she lived. We had a great time at Saguaro National Park, and had some nice meals out, not to mention a nice concert -- twice. 
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>October 2004 in Venice, Slovenja, Croatia and Montenegro</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/BalkansTrip2004/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>gondola.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            After visiting Croatia for the first time for an international conference in 2002, Ed wanted to go back to explore some more.  This trip started with three days in Venice, continued in the Jullian Alps in Slovenja, then down the Dalmation Coast of Croatia with a brief stop where Bosnia touches about a mile of the Adriatic shore, eventually reaching the beautiful walled city of Dubrovnic.  From Dubrovnic, we took a day trip to the Bay of Kotor in Montenegro, then part of Serbia.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>September 2004 Road Trip to Nova Scotia</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2004d-nova_scotia_trip/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>bluenose.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            Just before leaving for our Dalmation Coast trip, we took a road trip with Bill and Roz in Nova Scotia for a week, taking the high speed ferry from Bar Harbor, Maine and making a loop from Yarmouth to Halifax before returning home.
        </description>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>May 2004 Trip to Utah</title>
        <url>http://www.edburdick.net/Picturelib/2004b-utah_trip/index.html</url>
        <thumbnail>zion.jpg</thumbnail>
        <description>
            On the way back from a business trip to Oregon, I took a side trip to St. George, Utah to visit family and do some hiking in the area parks, including Zion and Snow Canyon. I had bought my first digital camera in Oregon on the same trip, so this was a good chance to try it out.
        </description>
    </entry>

</page>